esc4.net 2017-12-01

# 

**Disclaimer/Limitations of Liability**

The Region 4 Education Service Center website is intended for use by the general public as a convenient way to access the information and services provided by the Center. Efforts are made to ensure that the information presented is complete and accurate. However, the information and services included in or available through the Center's website may include inaccuracies or typographical errors. The website is periodically updated, corrected or otherwise modified at Region 4’s sole discretion and without notice. Any concerns regarding the accuracy of the information posted on this website should be directed to [website@esc4.net](mailto:website@esc4.net).

Region 4 Education Service Center does not represent or warrant that the website will be uninterrupted or error-free, that defects will be corrected, or that the website or the server that makes it available, are free of viruses, malware,  or other harmful components.

Region 4 strives to minimize cache issues, unauthorized modifications, and input errors.  However, several factors can affect the quality and timeliness of the information displayed on this Web site that are beyond the Center’s control—including browser incompatibilities; information which has been cached on the local computer, search engines, network proxy, or other storage device; unauthorized modification of electronic data; errors in transmission; or other issues with Web transmission.

Region 4 Education Service Center makes no representations about the suitability, reliability, availability, timeliness, or accuracy of the website for any purpose. The website and information contained herein are provided "as is" without warranty of any kind. Region 4 Education Service Center disclaims all warranties and conditions with regard to the service, including all implied warranties and conditions of merchantability of fitness for a particular purpose, title and non-infringement.

For security purposes, and to maintain service for all users, Region 4’s network system may use software programs to identify attempts to gain unauthorized access or to damage or misuse the systems of the Center’s web site. In the event that a potential security threat is recognized, identifying information about the user and the questionable computer actively may be retained and reviewed for security and other law-enforcement-related purposes.   
  
---  

**Privacy Policy**  

**Overview**

Region 4 respects the privacy of our online visitors and will post any changes to this policy here. By using the Region 4 website, you consent to the collection and use of information as described in the current policy. Under some circumstances, Region 4 may be compelled to disclose such information in accordance with the Texas Public Information Act or other legal or administrative requirements.

Region 4 does not collect personal information about website visitors unless you choose to provide that information to us as part of an inquiry, request or order.  Should you provide such information, you are giving Region 4 permission to use that information to complete your inquiry, request or order.

Region 4 does not sell personal information to outside parties. Region 4 will not release e-mail addresses that you provide to us to outside parties except as may be required by the Texas Public information Act or as may be required by law to protect Region 4’s legal rights.  

**Personal Information**

Region 4 does not collect any specific personal information about website visitors—such as name, postal address, or e-mail address—except when such information is knowingly, and voluntarily, provided to Region 4. Personal information is obtained from online transactions such as professional development registrations, online purchases, e-mail newsletters, online surveys, membership purchases, or employment or admissions applications. If Region 4 is provided with such information, you are giving Region 4  permission to use that information to respond to or process your request. For monetary transactions the financial aspect of the transaction is temporarily stored until the transaction has been completed then purged according to standard PCI practices.

Region 4 automatically collects and stores "non-personally identifiable" information for statistical purposes. This information helps Region 4 monitor how visitors use the site. This information may include: your browser software (e.g., Internet Explorer, Mozilla, Netscape Navigator), operating system (e.g., Windows or Macintosh), name and domain of your Internet Service Provider (e.g., AOL, NET.com), and the Internet Protocol (IP) address of the computer you are using.  

**Security**

The Region 4 website uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption to process registrations and all online purchases. This encryption prevents sensitive credit card information from being seen as it travels across the Internet to our servers, therefore making it difficult for anyone to intercept or decode messages exchanged over this secure connection. Credit card information is not permanently stored on the web server. Your order information, excluding private payment information, is retained for our records, but is never shared with other organizations or people.  

**Intellectual Property Rights**

The content contained within this website including, but not limited to, text, software, music, sound, photographs, video, graphics, or other material, may be protected by copyrights, trademarks, service marks, patents, or other proprietary rights and laws. Unless otherwise noted, Region 4 Education Service Center maintains intellectual property rights to all content on the website. For use permissions or information contact [website@esc4.net](mailto:website@esc4.net).  

**Links**

The Region 4 website contains links to other websites. Although every effort is made to ensure that all links are reputable and relevant, Region 4 is not responsible for the content or practices that appear on these third party sites. Once you leave the Region 4 website, you are subject to the privacy policy of the website containing that document. Region 4 encourages visitors to review the privacy policies of any sites they visit to ensure their personal information is being protected.  

**Updates**

The Region 4 Legal Disclaimers/Privacy Policy may be updated or revised from time to time without notice. We encourage you to check for updates each time you access the Region 4 Education Service Center Website.  

**Acceptance of terms**

By using the Region 4 Education Service Center website, you agree to the terms of our privacy policy. Region 4 Education Service Center reserves the right to change this privacy policy at any time, and changes posted on the website will be effective immediately.  

**Contacting us**

If you have questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, or request access to or changes to information about you, please contact us:

E-mail: [website@esc4.net](mailto:website@esc4.net)  
Region 4 Education Service Center Website  
7145 West Tidwell Road  
Houston, Texas 77092
